Hi everyone and welcome to this video. It's a shooting behind the scenes video
because today I have a photo shooting and I'm at a different location here.
I'm taking some pictures. This is the first outfit and I'm going to take you with me a bit.
I made sports on the knees so my knees look like this.
Oops, sorry.
I guess Photoshop.
We'll be right back.
Okay, that was the third outfit.
I think we have a few more to go and it's cool and the location is nice.
And yeah, we have to hurry but we only rented it for like four hours.
Okay, we're done for today. This is the last set. Not going to take off the mask because
then the makeup will be ruined. But yeah, it was fun and I hope you enjoyed this little
sneak peek behind the scenes, behind the cameras. And I'm going to have dinner now. See ya!
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!